androidapksfree.com 2019-11-07

# Privacy Policy - AndroidAPKsFree

At androidapksfree.com (“androidapksfree”, “website”, “we” or “us”), the privacy of our users is of extreme importance to us. This privacy policy document outlines the types of personal information is received and collected by us and how it is used.

## What personal data we collect and why we collect it

The personal data we collect about you is outlined in the following subsections:

### Comments

When visitors leave comments on the site we collect the data shown in the comments form, and also the visitor’s IP address and browser user agent string and referrer to help spam detection. We use spam detection service Akismet, and we collect above mentioned information about visitors who comment on Sites that use our Akismet anti-spam service. Their policy is available at: <https://automattic.com/privacy-notice/>

An anonymized string created from your email address (also called a hash) may be provided to the Gravatar service to see if you are using it. The Gravatar service privacy policy is available here: <https://automattic.com/privacy/>. After approval of your comment, your profile picture is visible to the public in the context of your comment.

### Contact forms

If you contact us by our contact form available [here](https://androidapksfree.com/contact/), you have to provide us your name, email address and choose a subject why you are contacting us and your message. Your email address will not be published. The information provided through the contact form will not be used for any marketing purposes, it will just be used to reach out to you regarding your message.

### Analytics and log files

Like many other Web sites, we make use of log files. The information inside the log files includes internet protocol ( IP ) addresses, type of browser, Internet Service Provider ( ISP ), date/time stamp, referring/exit pages, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user’s movement around the site, and gather demographic information. IP addresses, and other such information are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable. We use Google Analytics for analytics purposes.

### Cookies

We do use cookies to store information about visitors preferences, record user-specific information on which pages the user access or visit, customize Web page content based on visitors browser type or other information that the visitor sends via their browser.

If you leave a comment on our site you may opt-in to saving your name, email address and website in cookies. These are for your convenience so that you do not have to fill in your details again when you leave another comment. These cookies will last for one year.

If you have an account and you log in to this site, we will set a temporary cookie to determine if your browser accepts cookies. This cookie contains no personal data and is discarded when you close your browser.

When you log in, we will also set up several cookies to save your login information and your screen display choices. Login cookies last for two days, and screen options cookies last for a year. If you select “Remember Me”, your login will persist for two weeks. If you log out of your account, the login cookies will be removed.

You may read about the cookies used by Google analytics [here](https://developers.google.com/analytics/devguides/collection/analyticsjs/cookie-usage). If you want to prevent your data being used by Google Analytics, you can opt-out by installing the add-on for your web browser using: <https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout>

**Google/DoubleClick DART Cookie/Information Collection  
**

Third party vendors, including Google, use cookies to serve ads based on a user’s prior visits to our website or other websites.

Google’s use of advertising cookies enables it and its partners to serve ads to users based on their visit to our website and/or other websites on the Internet.

You may opt out of personalized advertising by visiting [Ads Settings](https://www.google.com/settings/ads). (Alternatively, you can opt out of a third-party vendor’s use of cookies for personalized advertising by visiting [www.aboutads.info](http://www.aboutads.info/choices/).)

Some of our advertising partners may use cookies and web beacons on our site. These third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology to the advertisements and links that appear on our website send directly to your browsers. They automatically receive your IP address when this occurs. Other technologies ( such as cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons ) may also be used by the third-party ad networks to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and/or to personalize the advertising content that you see.

We and third-party vendors, including Google, use first-party cookies (such as the Google Analytics cookies) and third-party cookies (such as the DoubleClick cookie) together to report how ad impressions, other uses of ad services, and interactions with these ad impressions and ad services are related to visits to our website.

### Switching off cookies

If you wish to disable cookies, you may do so through your individual browser options. More detailed information about cookie management and behavioural advertising is available here:

### Embedded content from other websites and Social networks

Articles on this site may include embedded content (e.g. videos, images, articles, etc.). Embedded content from other websites behaves in the exact same way as if the visitor has visited the other website.

These websites may collect data about you, use cookies, embed additional third-party tracking, and monitor your interaction with that embedded content, including tracing your interaction with the embedded content if you have an account and are logged in to that website.

## How long we retain your data

If you leave a comment, the comment and its metadata are retained indefinitely. This is so we can recognize and approve any follow-up comments automatically instead of holding them in a moderation queue.

For users that register on our website (if any), we also store the personal information they provide in their user profile. All users can see, edit, or delete their personal information at any time (except they cannot change their username). Website administrators can also see and edit that information.

## What rights you have over your data

If you have an account on this site, or have left comments, you can request to receive an exported file of the personal data we hold about you, including any data you have provided to us. You can also request that we erase any personal data we hold about you. This does not include any data we are obliged to keep for administrative, legal, or security purposes.

## Where we send your data

Visitor comments may be checked through an automated spam detection service.

## Terms of Service

You agree to our [terms and conditions](https://androidapksfree.com/terms/) by using our service.

## Contact information

If you require any more information or have any questions about our privacy policy, please feel free to contact us by email at contact [at] androidapks.com

You can reach us about your privacy concern using our [contact form](https://androidapksfree.com/contact/) and choose the subject “Privacy Concern”. You may also email us directly at the email address provided above.
